<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kdf</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kdiskfree</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDiskFree</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDiskFreexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDiskFree</name>
  <summary>View Disk Usage</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Veure l'ús de disc</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Veure l'ús de disc</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zobrazení využití disku</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Festplattenbelegung anzeigen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">View Disk Usage</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Visor de uso del disco</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ikusi diskoaren erabilera</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Näytä levynkäyttö</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Visualiser l'occupation du disque</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Visor do uso dos discos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Vide uso de disco</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visualizza l'utilizzo del disco</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">디스크 사용량 보기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Schijfgebruik bekijken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Vis diskbruk</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Informacja o wolnym miejscu na dyskach</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Visualização do Uso do Disco</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização do uso do disco</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Статистика использования дисков</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zobraziť využitie disku</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visa hårddiskanvändning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Перегляд використання диска</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxView Disk Usagexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">查看磁盘使用状况</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
     KDiskFree displays the available file devices (hard drive partitions, floppy and CD drives, etc.) along with information on their capacity, free space, type and mount point. It also allows you to mount and unmount drives and view them in a file manager.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDiskFree mostra els dispositius de fitxers disponibles (particions de disc dur, disquets i unitats de CD, etc.) juntament amb informació de la seva capacitat, espai lliure, tipus i punt de muntatge. També permet muntar i desmuntar les unitats i veure-les en un gestor de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KDiskFree mostra els dispositius de fitxers disponibles (particions de disc dur, disquets i unitats de CD, etc.) juntament amb informació de la seua capacitat, espai lliure, tipus i punt de muntatge. També permet muntar i desmuntar les unitats i veure-les en un gestor de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KDiskFree zeigt die verfügbaren Plattenbereiche an (Partitionen auf Festplatten, Disketten, CD-Laufwerke, USB-Sticks usw.). Zu jedem Bereich wird die Gesamtgröße, der freie Bereich, das Dateisystem und der Ort des Einhängens ins Dateisystem (Einhängepunkt) angezeigt. Mit KDiskFree können auch (sofern die Berechtigung vorhanden ist) Laufwerke ein- bzw. ausgehängt und die Dateiverwaltung mit der Anzeige für dieses Laufwerk geöffnet werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDiskFree displays the available file devices (hard drive partitions, floppy and CD drives, etc.) along with information on their capacity, free space, type and mount point. It also allows you to mount and unmount drives and view them in a file manager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDiskFree muestra los dispositivos de archivos disponibles (particiones de disco duro, disquetes, unidades de CD, etc.), junto a información sobre su capacidad, espacio libre, tipo y punto de montaje. También le permite montar y desmontar dispositivos, así como abrirlos en un gestor de archivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KDiskFreek erabilgarri dauden fitxategi gailuak azaltzen ditu (disko zurrun partizioak, diskete eta CD unitateak, etab.), haien gaitasuna, leku askea, mota, eta muntatze-puntuari buruzko informazioarekin batera. Unitateak muntatzea eta desmuntatzea eta haiek fitxategi-kudeatzailean ikustea eskaintzen du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KDiskFree näyttää saatavilla olevat tiedostolaitteet (kiintolevyosiot, levyke- ja CD-asemat jne.) tietoineen: kapasiteetti, vapaa tila, tyyppi ja liitospiste. Se antaa myös liittää ja irrottaa asemia ja katsoa niitä tiedostonhallinnassa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDiskFree affiche les systèmes de fichiers disponibles (partitions du disque dur, lecteurs disquettes/CD/DVD, etc.) ainsi que des informations sur leur capacité, l'espace disponible, leur type et leur point de montage. L'outil vous permet également de monter, de libérer et d'afficher les lecteurs dans un gestionnaire de fichiers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KDiskFree mostra os dispositivos de ficheiros dispoñíbeis (particións de discos duros, lectores de disquetes e CD, etc.) xunto con información sobre a súa capacidade, espazo libre, tipo e punto de montaxe. Tamén permite montar e desmontar lectores e velos no xestor de ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDiskFree mostra i dispositivi file disponibili (partizioni dei dischi fissi, unità a dischetti e lettori CD, eccetera) insieme ad informazioni sulla loro capacità, sullo spazio libero, sul tipo e sul punto di montaggio. Permette anche di montare e di smontare le unità e di visualizzarle in un gestore di file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDiskFree는 하드 드라이브 파티션, CD 및 플로피 드라이브 등 저장 장치의 크기, 사용 가능한 공간, 마운트 지점 등 정보를 표시합니다. 장치 마운트를 관리하고 파일 관리자로 열 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDiskFree toont de beschikbare apparaten voor bestandsopslag (vaste-schijfpartities, diskette- en -stations, USB-sticks, cd-station, etc.), met informatie over hun capaciteit, vrije ruimte, type en aankoppelpunt. Het geeft u ook de mogelijkheid om schijven aan- en af te koppelen en ze in een bestandsbeheerder te bekijken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KDiskFree viser lagringseiningar – for eksempel harddiskpartisjonar, diskettar og CD-plater – med informasjon om kapasitet, plassbruk, type og monteringspunkt. Det kan òg montera og avmontera einingar og opna dei i filhandsamaren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KDiskFree wyświetla dostępne urządzenia plikowe (partycje dysków twardych, dyskietki i napędy CD, itp.) wraz z informacją o ich pojemności, wolnej przestrzeni, rodzaju i punkcie podpięcia. Umożliwia podpinanie i odpinanie napędów, a także przeglądanie ich w przeglądarce plików.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDiskFree mostra os dispositivos de ficheiros disponíveis (partições de discos rígidos, unidades de disquetes e CD's, etc.) em conjunto com informações sobre a sua capacidade, espaço livre, tipo e ponto de montagem. Também lhe permite montar e desmontar as unidades e vê-las num gestor de ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDiskFree mostra os dispositivos de arquivos disponíveis (partições de discos rígidos, unidades de disquetes e CDs, dispositivos USB, etc.) juntamente com informações sobre sua capacidade, espaço livre, tipo e ponto de montagem. Também permite a montagem e desmontagem de unidades e visualizá-las em um gerenciador de arquivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KDiskFree служит для просмотра информации о доступных файловых устройствах (таких как разделы жёсткого диска, дискеты и приводы компакт-дисков): объём, доступное свободное место, тип и точка подключения. Кроме того, приложение позволяет подключать и отключать диски и открывать их для просмотра в приложении для управления файлами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kdiskfree visar tillgängliga filenheter (hårddiskpartitioner, diskett- och cd-enheter, etc.) tillsammans med information om deras kapacitet, ledigt utrymme, typ och monteringsplats. Det låter dig också montera och avmontera enheter och visa dem i en filhanterare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDiskFree показує список доступних файлових пристроїв (розділів жорсткого диска, пристроїв читання гнучких дисків, компакт-дисків, флеш-карток USB тощо), а також інформацію щодо їх місткості, вільного місця, типу і точки монтування. Ця програма також надає вам можливість монтувати, демонтувати пристрої і переглядати їх вміст у програмі для роботи з файлами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDiskFree displays the available file devices (hard drive partitions, floppy and CD drives, etc.) along with information on their capacity, free space, type and mount point. It also allows you to mount and unmount drives and view them in a file manager.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KDiskFree 显示所有的文件设备 (硬盘分区，软盘和 CD 驱动器等) 及他们的容量，可用空间，类型和挂载点。它也允许您挂载及卸载驱动器，以及在文件管理器中查看它们。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdf</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kdf&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kdf</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://utils.kde.org/projects/kdf/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>KDiskFree main window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal del KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal del KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Hauptfenster von KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">KDiskFree main window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">KDiskFreen pääikkuna</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xanela principal de KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Finestra principale di KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Hovudvindauge for KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Okno główne KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Janela principal do KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Janela principal do KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно приложения KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönstret i Kdiskfree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно KDiskFree</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxKDiskFree main windowxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">KDiskFree 主窗口</caption>
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/kdiskfree.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kdf</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kdf.desktop</launchable>
</component>
